Guide to the Washington State University Office of the President: Charles Clement French Records 1957-1966
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
Washington State University Office of the President: Charles Clement French Records
1957-1966
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives and Special Collections
Archives 203
Washington State University. Office of the President
27 Linear feet of shelf space 27 Boxes
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, reports and attached materials of the State College of Washington (later Washington State University) Office of the President during the C. Clement French administration.
The functions and duties of the Washington State University President are defined in University Faculty Manual, edition of 1987, as:
In addition to being designated as secretary ex officio of the Board of Regents, the President as general agent of the Board is the chief executive officer of Washington State University. The President administers the policies approved by the Board of Regents, serves as advisor to the Board on policies and operations and is the agent through whom representations to the Board are regularly made. Other functions of the chief executive officer include: Leadership in developing policies and organization for teaching, research, and extension programs. Public administration of the University, including representation before the Legislature and other state agencies. Responsibility for the general welfare of students; the development, operation and maintenance of buildings, lands and equipment; financial matters pertaining to development, operation and maintenance of University; and the administration of regulations adopted by the Board of Regents. Responsibility, delegated by the Board of Regents, for all appointments, promotion, salaries, leaves, resignations, and dismissals. Presiding at meetings of the general faculty.
Charles Clement French was born in 1901 in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania. French held three degrees in chemistry from the University of Pennsylvania, including a Ph.D. in physical chemistry. In 1925, French married Helen Augusta Black (1902-1976) and they had two children.
He was dean of the college at Randolph Macon College in Virginia, an administrator at Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Virginia Tech), and vice president at Texas Agricultural and Mechanical College (Texas A&M). In 1952 French was selected to be the sixth President of the State College of Washington (which was renamed Washington State University during his term).
French served as chairman of the Western Interstate Commission on Higher Education, and the Washington State Constitutional Revision Commission, as well as being a member of the Board of Trustees for the Century 21 Exposition (Seattle World's Fair). He retired in 1966 and was honored in 1968 with the university's new administration building being named for him. He received honorary degrees from Whitworth College, Pacific Lutheran University, and the University of Punjab. French died in Pullman, Washington in 1988.
The records consist of correspondence, memoranda, reports and attached materials of the State College of Washington (later Washington State University) Office of the President during the C. Clement French administration.
Organized in the original annual, alphabetical, subject files as received. One anomaly exists in this arrangement: the records from 1957, 1958, 1961 and 1961 appear to have been taken from the original subject folders by office staff and combined in folders each of which holds the contents of what had once been several original subject folders. The result is a sparse alphabetical filing system.
This collection is open and available for research use.
The records were transferred from the WSU Office of the President to the University Libraries in 1984 (Accession UA84-29) according to procedures outlined in an approved records schedule.
Charles Clement French Papers, 1914-1971 (Cage 310)
Charles Clement French Papers, 1967-1969 (Cage 490)
Charles Clement French Century 21 Exposition Planning Records, 1958-1962 (Cage 727)
State College of Washington Office of the President: Wilson Compton and Charles Clement French Records, 1948-1956 (Archives 12)
Washington State University Office of the President: Assistant to the President Records, 1954-1985 (Archives 216)
Washington State University Office of the President Media, 1937-2006 (Archives 328)
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
French, C. Clement (Charles Clement), 1901-1988 -- Archives; French, C. Clement (Charles Clement), 1901-1988
State College of Washington. Office of the President -- Records and correspondence; Washington State University. Office of the President -- Records and correspondence; State College of Washington -- Presidents -- Records and correspondence; Washington State University -- Presidents -- Records and correspondence; State College of Washington. Office of the President
College presidents -- Washington (State) -- Pullman
Colleges and Universities; Washington (State)
- 1957
  - A-C, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - C, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - D-I, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5-10)
  - K-N, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 11-14)
  - P-S, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 15-18)
  - S, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - T-W, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 20-23)
  - X-Z, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- 1958
  - A-C, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 25-27)
  - C-F, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 28-31)
  - F-P, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 32-42)
  - P-Q, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 43-44)
  - R-S, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 45-46)
  - S-W, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 47-51)
  - Y-Z, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 52-53)
- 1959
  - A, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Attorney for WSU, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - B-C, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 56-57)
  - Consolidated Investment Funds, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - D-F, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 59-61)
  - Financial information, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - G-L, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 63-68)
  - Land, Golden Bell, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Land acquisitions, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Land-grant colleges and universities, Centennial material, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - M-N, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 72-73)
  - P, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Pakistan, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Q-R, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 76-77)
  - Regents, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - S, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - State, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - State: Senate Bill No. 1, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - T, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Veterinary medicine, College of, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - W, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- 1960
  - A, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Building names, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - C-D, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 87-88)
  - Dairy Science Dept.: Dairy cattle testing, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Dean of Faculty, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Dean of Faculty: Staffing formula comparisons, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Dean of Students, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - E-F, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 93-94)
  - Financial information and bonds, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Fort George Wright, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - H-J, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 97-99)
  - KWSC, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - L, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Land: Golden bell, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Land acquisitions, leases, etc., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Library, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Military science and tactics, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Neill, Marshall A., Attorney General, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - News bureau, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - P, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Pakistan, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Regents, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - S, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Technology, Institute of, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - U.S. Government, Housing and home finance agency, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - U.S. Government, Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Universities and Colleges, Miscellaneous, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - W, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 116)
- 1961
  - A-F, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 117-122)
  - Financial information, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - French -- President, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - G-I, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 125-127)
  - International athletics, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 128)
  - J-L, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 129-131)
  - Land acquisition, leases, etc., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 132-133)
  - M-P, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 134-135)
  - P-S, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 136-139)
  - S, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 140)
  - Technology, Institute of, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 141)
  - U, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 142)
  - Universities and Colleges, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 143)
  - V-W, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 144-145)
  - X-Y-Z, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 146)
- 1962
  - A, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 147)
  - Admissions, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 148)
  - Admissions, Junior colleges, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 149)
  - Advisory boards technology, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 150)
  - Agricultural Experiment Stations, Irrigation, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 151)
  - Agricultural Experiment Stations, Office of the directors, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 152)
  - Agricultural Experiment Stations, Tree fruit, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 153)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 154)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, Snohomish Country, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Institute of, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - American Council on Education, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Animal Science, Dept. of, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Annual review, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Architect, University, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - ASWSU, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 161)
  - Athletic Association of Western Universities, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 162)
  - College entrance examination board, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 163)
  - Committees
    - Academic program, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Board of control, ASWSU, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Catalog Subcommittee of EPC, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 166)
    - Commencement, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 167)
    - Committee on committees, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Distinguished alumnus, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Honors council, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - International Education, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Ten-year planning, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 173)
  - Complaints, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 174)
  - Compton Union, Wilson, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 175)
  - Consolidated endowment fund, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 176)
  - Dean of Students, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 177)
  - Dean of the Faculty, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 178)
  - Dean of the Faculty: Small classes, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 179)
  - Engineering and Mineral Technology, College of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 180)
  - Financial information, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 181)
  - Financial information: salary schedules, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 182-183)
  - Fine Arts, Dept. of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 184)
  - Ford Foundation, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 185)
  - G, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 186)
  - Graduate Records, Office of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 187)
  - Graduate School, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 188)
  - H, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Information, Office of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Intercollegiate athletics, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - L, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Land acquisition, leases, etc., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Land-grant Colleges and State Universities, Association of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Land-grant Colleges and State Universities, Association of, Centennial material, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Library, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 196)
  - M, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - P, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 198)
  - Pakistan, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Pharmacy, College of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - President's office, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Regents, Board of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 202)
  - Registrar: Enrollment statistics, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Research Corporation, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - S, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 205)
  - State: Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Student Health Service, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Students Book Store, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - U.S.: Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - U.S.: Miscellaneous, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - U.S. Defense, Dept. of (Air Force advisory panel), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 211)
  - U.S. Health, Education, and Welfare, Dept. of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - U.S. Interior, Dept. of, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 213)
  - U.S. Peace Corps, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - U.S. Senators and Representatives, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Universities and Colleges: Washington State Institutions (5), 1962 (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - W, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - XYZ, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 218)
- 1963
  - A, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - Admissions, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Admissions: High school visitation, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - Admissions: Junior colleges, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - Advisory boards
    - Agricultural sciences, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Sanitary engineering, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Technology, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Veterinary medicine, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 226)
  - Agricultural Chemistry, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 227)
  - Agricultural Economics, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 228)
  - Agricultural Engineering, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 229)
  - Agricultural Experiment stations
    - Irrigation, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - Northern Washington, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - Office of Director, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - Southwestern Washington, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Western Washington, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 234)
  - Agricultural Extension Service, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Agricultural Extension Service: 4-H club, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Agricultural Sciences, Institute of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Agriculture, College of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Agronomy, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - American Assembly, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 241)
  - American Association of University Women, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 242)
  - American Council on Education, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - American Studies, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Animal Science, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Annual review, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Applications, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Architect, University, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 248)
  - Architect, University: Space analyst, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Architectural Engineering, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - ASWSU, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Athletic Association of Western Universities, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Audio-visual Center, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - B, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Bacteriology and Public Health, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Biological sciences annex: Research facilities, B. Roger Ray, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Botany, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Budget office, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 258)
  - Building names, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Buildings and Grounds, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Business Administration, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Business Manager, Office of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - C, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 263)
  - Chamber of Commerce, miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 264)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Pullman, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 265)
  - Chemical Engineering, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 266)
  - Chemistry, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 267)
  - Civil Engineering, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - College Entrance Examination Board, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Committees
    - Academic program, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Academic relations with Washington colleges, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - Academic standing, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 272)
    - Catalog subcommittee of EPC, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 273)
    - Commencement, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 274)
    - Distinguished alumnus award, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 275)
    - Educational policies, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 276)
    - Faculty executive, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 277)
    - Freshmen-faculty weekend, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 278)
    - Health and safety, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 279)
    - Honors council, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 280)
    - International education, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 281)
    - Isotopes, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 282)
    - Lecture-artist, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 283)
    - Library advisory, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 284)
    - Miscellaneous, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 285)
    - Patent, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 286)
    - Research, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 287)
    - Space Priorities, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 288)
    - Ten-year planning, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 289)
    - Traffic control board, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 290)
  - Complaints, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 291)
  - Computing Center, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Compton Union, Wilson, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Comptroller, Office of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - Consolidated endowment fund, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - Cougar clubs, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Council of State Governments, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - D, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Diary Science, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Data Processing, Office of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Dean, Directors, and Department Chairman, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - Dean of Students, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 302)
  - Dean of the Faculty, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 303)
  - Dean of the Faculty
    - Academic report, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 304)
    - Grade studies, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 305)
    - Improvement of instruction, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 306)
    - Invited lectures (WSU faculty), 1963 (Box 8, Folder 307)
    - Small classes, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 308)
    - Teaching loading studies, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 309)
  - Dormitory for women, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 310)
  - E, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 311)
  - Economic and Business Research, Bureau of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 312)
  - Economics, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - Economics and Business, College of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 314)
  - Education, College of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Electrical Engineering, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Electron Microscope, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - Engineering, College of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - English, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - Entomology, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 320)
  - F, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Faculty and staff, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Faculty orientation, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Financial information, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Financial information: Cost studies, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 325)
  - Financial information: Salary schedules, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 326)
  - Financial information: Tuition and fees, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 327)
  - Fine Arts, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 328)
  - Food Science, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 329)
  - Football
    - WSU -- Arizona, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 330)
    - WSU -- Idaho, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 331)
    - WSU -- Oregon, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 332)
    - WSU -- Oregon State, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 333)
    - WSU -- San Jose, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 334)
    - West Point, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 335)
  - Ford Foundation, The, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - Foreign Languages, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - Forestry and Range Management, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 338)
  - G, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - General Education and Curriculum Advisory Program, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 340-341)
  - General reserve, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 342)
  - General Telephone Company of the Northwest, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - Genetics, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - General Telephone Company of the Northwest, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - Genetics, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - Geology, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 345)
  - Governing boards of State universities and allied institutions, Association of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - Graduate School, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Graduate Records, Office of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 348)
  - H, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 349)
  - High school summer camp, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 350)
  - History, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 351)
  - Home Economics, College of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 352)
  - Horticulture, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 353)
  - Housing and Food service, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 354)
  - Hydraulics laboratory addition, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - I, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 356)
  - Industrial Research, Division of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Information, Office of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - Information Science, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 359)
  - Intercollegiate athletics, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 360)
  - Interfraternity alumni: Advisors association, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 361)
  - Interfraternity Council, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - International Student Office, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 363)
  - J, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Journalism, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - K, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 366)
  - KWSC: Radio and television, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 367)
  - L, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 368)
  - Land acquisitions, leases, etc., 1963 (Box 10, Folder 369)
  - Land-grant Association, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 370)
  - Land-grant Association: Centennial material, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 371)
  - Land-grant Association: Joint Office of Institutional, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 372)
  - Library, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 373)
  - Library, Friends of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 374)
  - M, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 375)
  - Mathematics, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 376)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 377)
  - Military Coordinator: Air Science, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 378)
  - Military Coordinator: Military Science, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 379)
  - Music, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 380)
  - N, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 381)
  - National Association of State Universities, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 382)
  - National Education Association, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 383-384)
  - Neill, Marshall A., 1963 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - Northwest Association of Secondary and Higher Schools, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 386)
  - Nuclear reactor, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 387)
  - O, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 388)
  - Oregon, State of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 389)
  - P, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 390)
  - Pacific Northwest Conference on Higher Education, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 391)
  - Pacific Science Center Foundation committee, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  - Pakistan, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 393)
  - Pharmacy, College of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 394)
  - Philosophy, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 395)
  - Physical Education and Recreation, College of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - Physical Education and Recreation for Men, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 397)
  - Physical Education and Recreation for Women, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - Physics, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 399)
  - Placement Bureau, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 400)
  - Plant Pathology, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 401)
  - Police Science and Administration, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 402)
  - Political Science, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Presidents office, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 404)
  - Property inventory, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 405)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 406)
  - Publications, Office of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 407)
  - Publications, Office of WSU news bulletin, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 408)
  - Pullman, City of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 409)
  - Pullman First National Bank, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 410)
  - Pullman Herald, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 411)
  - Pullman Public Schools, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 412)
  - Purchasing office, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 413)
  - Q, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 414)
  - R, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 415)
  - Recommendations, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 416)
  - Regents, Board of, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 417)
  - Registrar, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 418)
  - Registrar -- enrollment, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 419)
  - Research Corporation, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 420)
  - Research Foundation, WSU, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 421)
  - Reservations, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 422)
  - Resident instructional staff, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 423)
  - Retirement and Insurance office, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 424)
  - Retirements, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 425)